NWLB Region II Office Files and Cases 5311
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- 111-11537-HO Mack Int'l Motor Truck Corp., 1945 (Box 27, Folder 12)
- 111-2778-D Meadow Products, 1944 (Box 28, Folder 1)
- 111-2778-D Meadow Gold Products Folder 2, 1944 (Box 28, Folder 2)
- 111-6642-D Melville Shoe Corp., 1944-1945 (Box 28, Folder 3)
- 111-6642-D Melville Shoe Corp., 1944 (Box 28, Folder 4)
- 111-773-AR Mercer Engineering Works Inc., 1943 (Box 28, Folder 5)
- 111-2678-HO Merritt Engineering & Sales Co., Inc., 1943-1945 (Box 28, Folder 6)
- 111-8899-Metal & Thermit Corp., 1944 (Box 28, Folder 7)
- 2-D-82 Metal & Thermit Corp. 111-668-D, 1943 (Box 28, Folder 8)
- 111-6073-HO Metal and Roofing Distributors Association, 1945 (Box 28, Folder 9)
- 111-5620-D Metropolitan Container Council, Inc., 1945 (Box 28, Folder 10)
- 111-2826-D Metropolitan Life Insurance Company, 1944 (Box 28, Folder 11)
- 111-15969-HO Metropolitan Lumber Dealers Association, 1945 (Box 28, Folder 12)
- 111-8825-D Metropolitan Plate & Windown Glass Distributors, 1945 (Box 28, Folder 13)
- 111-418-C Midwest Piping & Supply Co., 1943 (Box 29, Folder 1)
- 111-7361-D Millinery Retailers Ass'n. if Greater New York, Inc., 1945 (Box 29, Folder 2)
- 111-12106-D Moench Tanning Co., 1945 (Box 29, Folder 3)
- 111-3092-D Monroe Calculating Machine Folder 1, 1944 (Box 29, Folder 4)
- 111-3092-D Monroe Calculating Machine Folder 2, 1944 (Box 29, Folder 5)
- 111-3092-D Monroe Calculating Machine Company. Folder 3, 1944-1945 (Box 29, Folder 6)
- 111-7793-D Montgomery Ward & Co., 1945 (Box 29, Folder 7)
- 111-12897-D Morrison Machine Co., 1943 (Box 29, Folder 8)
- 111-256-AR Motor Hearse & Car Owners Assn., Inc., 1943 (Box 29, Folder 9)
- 111-10535-D Mutual Box Board Company, 1945 (Box 29, Folder 10)
- 111-6132-D National Aniline Defense Corp., 1944 (Box 30, Folder 1)
- 111-5747-D Nat'l. Assn. of Leather Glove Mfrs., Inc. (FULTON Co. Br.), 1943-1945 (Box 30, Folder 2)
- 111-4452-D National Battery Co. Folder 1, 1943-1945 (Box 30, Folder 3)
- 111-4452-D National Battery Co. Folder 2, 1944-1945 (Box 30, Folder 4)
- 111-4452-D National Battery Co., 1943-1945 (Box 30, Folder 5)
- 111-11982-D National Battery Co., 1945 (Box 30, Folder 6)
- 111-3897-D National Bearing Metal Co., Inc., 1944 (Box 30, Folder 7)
- 111-12349-D National Bearing Metal Corp., 1945 (Box 30, Folder 8)
- 111-14851-HO National Biscut Co., 1945 (Box 30, Folder 9)
- 111-6661-D National Biscuit Co., 1944 (Box 31, Folder 1)
- 111-9838-JB National Biscuit Co., 1945 (Box 31, Folder 2)
- 111-7291-HO National Can Corp., 1944 (Box 31, Folder 3)
- 111-11710-D National Manufacturing Corp., 1945 (Box 31, Folder 4)
- 111-9234-HO National Sandust Company Inc., 1944-1945 (Box 31, Folder 5)
- 111-675-D National Metal Spinners Assn., Inc., 1944 (Box 31, Folder 6)
- 111-10817-D National Union Radio Corp., 1944-1945 (Box 31, Folder 7)
- 111-10817-D National Union Radio Corp., 1945 (Box 31, Folder 8)
- Manual of Operations - National War Labor Board Folder 1, 1943-1945 (Box 32, Folder 1)
- Manual of Operations - National War Labor Board Folder 2, 1943-1945 (Box 32, Folder 2)
- 111-405-C National Urn Bag Co. 2-D-44, 1944-1945 (Box 32, Folder 3)
- 111-4843-D National Velvet Corp., 1945 (Box 32, Folder 4)
- 111-7203-D R. Neumann and Company, 1945 (Box 32, Folder 5)
- 111-682-D New Jersey Brewing 2-D-84, 1943-1945 (Box 32, Folder 6)
- 111-2139-D Newark Baking Cos., 1944 (Box 32, Folder 7)
- 111-975-D New York Bakeries, 1943-1945 (Box 32, Folder 8)
- 111-15124-D New York Butchers Dressed Meat Company (Box 33, Folder 1)
- 111-6763-D New York Cafes & Night Clubs, 1945 (Box 33, Folder 2)
- Il-Bwa-15 New York Laundries, 1943-1945 (Box 33, Folder 3)
- 111-987-HO New York Employing Printer Assn., Inc., 1944-1945 (Box 33, Folder 4)
- 2-HO-170 New York Employing 111-1077-HO Printers Assn., Inc., 1943 (Box 33, Folder 5)
- 111-2827-D New York Hospital, 1944 (Box 33, Folder 6)
- 111-12802-D New York Iron Roofing & Corrugation Co., Inc., 1944 (Box 33, Folder 7)
- 111-4962-D New York Miling Cos. (5), 1944 (Box 33, Folder 8)
- 2-25514 N.Y.C. Omnibus Corp. Fifth Ave. Coach Co., 1943-1944 (Box 33, Folder 9)
- 111-12221-HO New York Quinine & Chemical Works Inc., 1945 (Box 33, Folder 10)
- War Labor Board - General Chemical Co., 1945 (Box 34, Folder 1)
- Steel Industry Prices, Profits, and Costs, 1943-1945 (Box 34, Folder 2)
- National War Labor Board Second Region, 1945 (Box 34, Folder 3)
- NWLB - Research and Statistics Reports, 1943-1945 (Box 34, Folder 4)
- Reply Brief Submitted by United Steelworkers of America to Panels of National War Labor Board, 1944 (Box 34, Folder 5)
- In the matter of General Chemical Company, Buffalo Works, and United Gas, Coke & Chemical Workers of America, Local No. 211, CIO., 1945 (Box 34, Folder 6)
- General Chemical Company, Buffalo Works and United Gas, Coke & Chemical Workers of America, Local No. 211, CIO., 1945 (Box 34, Folder 7)
- 111-1425-D New York Truckmen & Warehouse Group, 1944 (Box 34, Folder 8)
- 111-1425-D New York Truckmen & Warehouse Group, 1943-1945 (Box 34, Folder 9)
- 2-46694 Niagara Blower Co., 1944-1945 (Box 34, Folder 10)
- 111-1145-D Niagara Frontier Printers Assn., 1943 (Box 34, Folder 11)
- 111-2359-D Niagara Power Corp., 1944 (Box 34, Folder 12)
- 2nd region. War Labor Board Norwich Pharmacal Company and United Retail, Wholesale and Department Store Employees of America, C.I.O., Local 65, 1944 (Box 34, Folder 13)
- 111-11133-HO Old Dutch Mustard Co. Inc., 1945 (Box 34, Folder 14)
- 111-7114-AR Olsker Builders Supply & Coal Co., 1944 (Box 34, Folder 15)
- 111-2935-HO Ontario Biscuit Co., 1945 (Box 35, Folder 1)
- A-73 195 Broadway Corporation, 1942-1945 (Box 35, Folder 2)
- 111-9250-D Pantasote Leather Co., 1945 (Box 35, Folder 3)
- 2-23921 Paragon Glass works, 1943-1944 (Box 35, Folder 4)
- 2-76043 870 Seventh Ave. Corp. (Park Central Hotel), 1942-1945 (Box 35, Folder 5)
- 111-9776-HO Pequannock Valley Paper Company, 1945 (Box 35, Folder 6)
- 2-61381 Richel Inc., 1945 (Box 35, Folder 7)
- Permutit, 1944 (Box 35, Folder 8)
- 3945-CS-D Petroff (Peter A. Machinery & Tools), 1945 (Box 35, Folder 9)
- 111-5471-D Petroleum Heat & Power Company, 1945 (Box 35, Folder 10)
- 111-9785-D Pequanoc Rubber Company, 1945 (Box 35, Folder 11)
- 111-1448-D Phelps Dodge Copper Corp. Folder 1, 1945 (Box 36, Folder 1)
- 111-1448-D Phelps Dodge Copper Corp. Folder 2, 1944 (Box 36, Folder 2)
- Phelps Dodge Corporation 111-9934-D, 1945 (Box 36, Folder 3)
- 111-9934-D Phelps's Dodge Refining Corporation, 1945 (Box 36, Folder 4)
- 111-11916-D Phillips Petroleum Co., 1945 (Box 36, Folder 5)
- 111-2769-HO Phoenix Die Casting Company Inc., 1943-1945 (Box 36, Folder 6)
- 111-778-D Photo-Engravers Bd. Trade of N.Y., Inc., 1943 (Box 36, Folder 7)
- 111-4960-D Pillsbury Flour Mill Co. Folder 1, 1945 (Box 37, Folder 1)
- 111-4960-D Pillsbury Flour Mill Co. Folder 2, 1944 (Box 37, Folder 2)
- 111-5749-D Pitometer Log Corp., 1944 (Box 37, Folder 3)
- 111-1498-D Pitometer Log Corp., 1944 (Box 37, Folder 4)
- 111-3194-D Pratt & Letchworth Co., Inc., 1945 (Box 37, Folder 5)
- 111-3194-D Pratt and Letchworth Co., Inc., 1945 (Box 37, Folder 6)
- Dispute with Pratt and Letchworth; letters to Theodore Kheel, 1943 (Box 37, Folder 7)
- 111-3194-D Pratt & Letchworth Co., Inc., 1943-1945 (Box 37, Folder 8)
- 111-1235-D Poughkeepsie Foundry & Machine Co., 1943 (Box 37, Folder 9)
- 111-90-R Printers League Section of the N.Y. Employing Printers Ass'n., 1944 (Box 37, Folder 10)
- 111-685-AR Printers League Section, Etc., 1945 (Box 37, Folder 11)
- 14-311 Queen City Foundry & Machine Company, 1945 (Box 38, Folder 1)
- 111-8389-D Quigley Publishing Co., 1945 (Box 38, Folder 2)
- 111-13249-D Radio Development Research Corporation, 1945 (Box 38, Folder 3)
- 111-11795-D Radio Station W.O.V., 1945 (Box 38, Folder 4)
- 111-7546-D Rane Tool Company, Inc., 1945 (Box 38, Folder 5)
- 111-3819-D Random House, Inc., 1944 (Box 38, Folder 6)
- 111-1167-D Ranger Aircraft Engines Corp., 1943-1945 (Box 38, Folder 7)
- 111-774-D Reader Mill, Inc., 1944-1945 (Box 38, Folder 8)
- 111-6679-D Realty Advisory Board on Labor Relations, Inc., 1945 (Box 38, Folder 9)
- 111-6880-D Reilly Tar & Chemical Corp., 1945 (Box 38, Folder 10)
- 111-6882-D Remington Rand Inc., 1945 (Box 38, Folder 11)
- 111-4736-D Republic Steel Corp., 1944 (Box 39, Folder 1)
- Case No. 111-9833-HO U.G.C. & C. Local 115 vs. Republic Lt. Ht. & Pwr. Co., inc. (Box 39, Folder 2)
- 111-12801-D Republic Steel Company, 1945 (Box 39, Folder 3)
- 111-11135-JB Revere Copper & Brass Co, Inc., 1945 (Box 39, Folder 4)
- 111-11591-HO Revere Copper & Brass Company, Inc., 1945 (Box 39, Folder 5)
- 111-12031-HO Revere Copper & Brass Inc., 1945 (Box 39, Folder 6)
- 111-1974-D Richardson Company, 1945 (Box 39, Folder 7)
- 111-1974- Richardson Company, 1943-1944 (Box 39, Folder 8)
- 111-11019-D Richardson Company, 1945 (Box 39, Folder 9)
- 2-61617 Rheem Mfg. Co., 1945 (Box 39, Folder 10)
- 111-3692-D Richter (G.F.) Mfg. Co., 1944-1945 (Box 39, Folder 11)
- 111-3692-D Richter (G.F.) Mfg. Co. Folder 2, 1944-1945 (Box 39, Folder 12)
- Robins Conveyors, Incorporated Employer, -and- International Association of Machinists, Victory Lodge No. 1170, 1944 (Box 39, Folder 13)
- 111-1156-D Rockland Light & Power Co., 1944 (Box 39, Folder 14)
- 111-5020-D Rockland Light & Power Company, 1945 (Box 40, Folder 1)
- 111-10753-HO St. Regis Paper Company, 1945 (Box 40, Folder 2)
- 111-895-D San-Equip., Inc., 1943 (Box 40, Folder 3)
- 111-2245-D Schoanmaker (A.O.) Insulation Co., 1944 (Box 40, Folder 4)
- 2-38490 F.A.O. Schwarz Inc., 1944 (Box 40, Folder 5)
- 111-460-AR Sharpe, Inc. 2-AR-27, 1943 (Box 40, Folder 6)
- 111-10639-HO Sheffield Farms Company, Inc., 1945 (Box 40, Folder 7)
- 111-10431-D Sheffield Farms Co. Inc., 1945 (Box 40, Folder 8)
- 111-7473-D Shepard Niles Crane and Hoist Corp., 1944 (Box 40, Folder 9)
- 111-7473-D Shepard Miles Crane and Hoist Corp. Folder 2, 1944 (Box 40, Folder 10)
- 111-916-AR Sheridan Iron Works, 1944 (Box 41, Folder 1)
- 111-4627-HO Sherron Metallic Corp., 1943 (Box 41, Folder 2)
- 111-13017-D Sherwin-Williams Company, 1945 (Box 41, Folder 3)
- 111-13017-D Sherwin-Williams Company Folder 2, 1945 (Box 41, Folder 4)
- Singer Mfg. Corp., 1945 (Box 41, Folder 5)
- 111-1906-D Skylar (J.) Mfg. Co., 1944 (Box 41, Folder 6)
- 111-10873-D Smith (Alexander) & Son Carpet Company, 1944-1945 (Box 41, Folder 7)
- 111-10873-D Smith (Alexander) & Son Carpet Company Folder 2, 1945 (Box 41, Folder 8)
- 111-749-D Sonoco Products Co., 1944 (Box 41, Folder 9)
- 111-7186-D Sparkman & Stephens., 1944-1945 (Box 42, Folder 1)
- 111-10686-HO Spaulding Bakeries, Inc., 1944 (Box 42, Folder 2)
- 111-12807-D Spaulding Bakeries Inc., 1945 (Box 42, Folder 3)
- 2-D-181 Spencer Lens Company 111-1184-D, 1944 (Box 42, Folder 4)
- 2-D-181 Spencer Lens Company 111-1184-D Folder 2, 1944 (Box 42, Folder 5)
- 111-285-C Spring Porch Co., 1943 (Box 42, Folder 6)
- 2-28705 Standard Brands Inc., 1944 (Box 42, Folder 7)
- 111-11734-D Stanley Tools, Inc., 1945 (Box 42, Folder 8)
- 111-14349-HO Sterling Engine Company, 1945 (Box 42, Folder 9)
- 111-10080-D Swift and Company, 1945 (Box 42, Folder 10)
- 111-10938-D Swift & Company, 1945 (Box 42, Folder 11)
- 111-11474-D Swift and Company, 1945 (Box 42, Folder 12)
- 111-9415-D Swift & Company (Ice Cream Division), 1945 (Box 42, Folder 13)
- 111-4983-D Swift & Company Folder 1, 1945 (Box 43, Folder 1)
- 111-4983-D Swift & Company Folder 2, 1945 (Box 43, Folder 2)
- 111-8302-HO Symington - Gould Corp., 1944 (Box 43, Folder 3)
- 111-8816-HO Tide Publishing Company, 1945 (Box 43, Folder 4)
- 111-12093-D Tidewater Associated Oil Company, 1945 (Box 43, Folder 5)
- 111-2438-D Tidewater Assoc. Oil Company, 1943-1944 (Box 43, Folder 6)
- 111-5660-D Tidewater Associated Oil Company, 1944 (Box 43, Folder 7)
- 111-9326-D Todd Company (Printing IMV), 1944 (Box 43, Folder 8)
- 111-3042-D Texas Company, 1944 (Box 43, Folder 9)
- 4257-D Texas Co., 1943 (Box 43, Folder 10)
- 111-13138-HO Towns & James Inc., 1945 (Box 44, Folder 1)
- 111-13188-HO Towns & James Inc., 1944-1945 (Box 44, Folder 2)
- 111-11683-D Union Abesto's and Rubber Company, 1945 (Box 44, Folder 3)
- 111-11434-HO Union Bag & Paper Corp., 1945 (Box 44, Folder 4)
- 111-9773-HO United Bristle Co, Inc., 1945 (Box 44, Folder 5)
- 111-17590-HO U.S. Industrial Chemical, Inc., 1945 (Box 44, Folder 6)
- 111-13526-D U.S. Metals Refining Company, 1945 (Box 44, Folder 7)
- 111913526-D U.S. Metal Refining Company Folder 2, 1945 (Box 44, Folder 8)
- 111-8278-D U.S. Tool Company, Inc. Folder 1, 1944-1945 (Box 44, Folder 9)
- 111-8278-D U.S. Tool Company, Inc. Folder 2, 1944-1945 (Box 44, Folder 10)
- 111-1904-D United Traction Co. Capital District Trans Co., 1944 (Box 45, Folder 1)
- Suppl. File 111-3898-D Waldes Koh-I-Noor, 1945 (Box 45, Folder 1)
- 111-4442-HO Urban (George) Milling Co., 1945 (Box 45, Folder 2)
- 111-7718-D Utica Knitting Corp. Folder 1, 1945 (Box 45, Folder 3)
- 111-7719-D Vanadium Corp. of Amer., 1945 (Box 45, Folder 4)
- 111-7714-D Vanadium Corp. of Amer., 1944-1945 (Box 45, Folder 5)
- 111-9876-HO Vascoloy-Ramet Corporation, 1945 (Box 45, Folder 6)
- Verdi Brothers Cooperage Co., 1945 (Box 45, Folder 7)
- 111-6775-HO Victor Steel Products Corporation, 1945 (Box 45, Folder 8)
- Labor Board Waldes Koh-I-Noor Folder 1, 1945 (Box 45, Folder 9)
- Labor Board Waldes Koh-I-Noor Folder 2, 1944-1945 (Box 45, Folder 10)
- Prepared and Submitted by Waldes Koh-I-Noor, Inc., 1945 (Box 45, Folder 11)
  Scope and Contents
  10 Photographs
- Wales-Strippit Corporation and United Electrical, Radio & Machine Workers of America, CIO, Local 308, 1944 (Box 46, Folder 1)
- 111-3044-D Wales Strippit Corp., 1944-1945 (Box 46, Folder 2)
- 111-3044-D Wales Strippit Corp. Folder 2, 1944-1945 (Box 46, Folder 3)
- 111-12502-D Wallington Tube Corporation, 1945 (Box 46, Folder 4)
- 111-7271-D Walter Motor Truck Co., 1945 (Box 46, Folder 5)
- 111-6831-D Ward Leonard Electric Company, 1944 (Box 46, Folder 6)
- 111-9472-D Ward Motor Vehicle Company, 1945 (Box 46, Folder 7)
- 111-6972-HO Warner Bros. Picture, 1944 (Box 46, Folder 8)
- 111-2383-HO Washington Fillmore Foundry, Inc., 1945 (Box 46, Folder 9)
- 111-1929-D Watson Flagg Machine Co., Inc., 1944 (Box 47, Folder 1)
- Case No. 111-16333-HO, 1945 (Box 47, Folder 2)
- 111-9534-HO Wesley & Winter Corp., 1944 (Box 47, Folder 3)
- 111-790-D Western Union Telegram Company, 1943 (Box 47, Folder 4)
- 111-3691-D Western Union Telegraph Company, 1945 (Box 47, Folder 5)
- 111-9960-HO Weston Biscuit Co., 1945 (Box 47, Folder 6)
- 2nd Region. War Labor Board Weston Electrical Instrument Corp. and Weston Employees Protective Association Independent Union Case No. 111-10834-D, 1944 (Box 47, Folder 7)
- 111-11364-HO Whippany Paperboard Company, 1944-1945 (Box 47, Folder 8)
- 111-15617-HO Whitelawn Diaries Inc., 1945 (Box 47, Folder 9)
- 111-3774-D Wickwire Bros. Inc., 1944 (Box 47, Folder 10)
- 111-8746-D Wid's Film & Film Folk, Inc., 1945 (Box 47, Folder 11)
- 111-8715-D 150 William Street Corp., 1945 (Box 48, Folder 1)
- 111-11289-D Wilson and Company, Inc., 1945 (Box 48, Folder 2)
- 111-11565-D Wilson Athletic Goods Mfg. Co., 1945 (Box 48, Folder 3)
- 111-2056-D Wood (Alan) Steel Co. Inc., 1943-1945 (Box 48, Folder 4)
- 111-10209-D World Bestos Corp., 1945 (Box 48, Folder 5)
- 111-6851-D World Steel Products, 1944 (Box 48, Folder 6)
- 111-4394-D Worthington Pump & Machinery Corp., 1943-1945 (Box 48, Folder 7)
- 111-3089-D Worthington Pump & Machinery Corp., 1944 (Box 49, Folder 1)
- Worthington Pump & Machinery Corp. vs. United Steelworkers of America District 4, 1943-1945 (Box 49, Folder 2)
- Worthington Pump & Doch. Corp: Case 14-589, 1943-1945 (Box 49, Folder 3)
- 111-2504-D Worthington Pump & Machinery Corp., 1943-1945 (Box 49, Folder 4)
- 111-11675-D Wright Aeronautical Corporation, 1944-1945 (Box 49, Folder 5)
- 111-11260-D Wright Aeronautical Corporation, 1944-1945 (Box 49, Folder 6)
- 111-1054-AR Zamax Mfg. Co. Inc., 1943 (Box 49, Folder 7)
- 111-6718-D Zimmer Thomson Corp., 1944 (Box 49, Folder 8)
- A - Correspondence 5/29/45 - 12/12/45, 1945 (Box 50, Folder 1)
- A - Correspondence 1/2/45- 5/31/45, 1945 (Box 50, Folder 2)
- B - Correspondence 5/1/45 - 12/13/45, 1945 (Box 50, Folder 3)
- B - Correspondence 1/1/45 -5/30/45, 1945 (Box 50, Folder 4)
- C - Correspondence 1/2/45 -5/31/45, 1945 (Box 50, Folder 5)
- C - Correspondence 6/1/45 - 12-21/45, 1945 (Box 50, Folder 6)
- E - Correspondence 1/3/45 -12/10/45, 1945 (Box 50, Folder 7)
- E - Correspondence 1/3/45 -12/5/45, 1945 (Box 50, Folder 8)
- F - Correspondence 1/3/45 - 12/7/45, 1945 (Box 50, Folder 9)
- G - Correspondence 1/3/45 -5/31/45, 1945 (Box 50, Folder 10)
- G Correspondence 5/28/45 -12/27/45, 1945 (Box 50, Folder 11)
- H - Correspondence 1/2/45 -5/31/45, 1945 (Box 50, Folder 12)
- H - Correspondence 6/5/45 - 12/5/45, 1945 (Box 50, Folder 13)
- I - Correspondence 1/10/45 -12/28/45, 1945 (Box 51, Folder 1)
- J - Correspondence 1/4/45 - 12/12/45, 1945 (Box 51, Folder 2)
- K - Correspondence 1/5/45 -12/5/45, 1945 (Box 51, Folder 3)
- L - Correspondence 1/6/45 -12/26/45, 1945 (Box 51, Folder 4)
- M - Correspondence 1/3/45 -4/25/45, 1945 (Box 51, Folder 5)
- M - Correspondence 5/1/45 - 12/27/45, 1945 (Box 51, Folder 6)
- N - Correspondence 1/2/45 -12/19/45 (Box 51, Folder 7)
- Q - Correspondence 7/9/45, 1945 (Box 51, Folder 8)
- Approvable Wage Rates, 1945 (Box 51, Folder 9)
- Cost of Living - Report of the President's Committee 11/10/44, 1944 (Box 51, Folder 10)
- Decisions, Second Regional War Labor Board, No. 1, 1945 (Box 51, Folder 11)
- F.#25 - Guaranteed Employment and Annual Wage Plans, 1946 (Box 51, Folder 12)
- Decisions, Second Regional War Labor Board, No. 2 10/45, 1945 (Box 51, Folder 13)
- Decisions, Second Regional War Labor Board, No. 3 11/45, 1945 (Box 51, Folder 14)
- Decisions, Second Regional War Labor Board, No. 4 12-45, 1945 (Box 51, Folder 15)
- History and Procedure 4/44, 1944 (Box 51, Folder 16)
- Inflation - Report to the President 4/7/45, 1945 (Box 51, Folder 17)
- Jurisdiction of the Board, 1945 (Box 51, Folder 18)
- Little Steel Formula - Application 1/44, 1944 (Box 51, Folder 19)
- Manual of Instructions, For Panel Members & Hearing Officers 11/1/43, 1943 (Box 51, Folder 20)
- Manual of Instructions, For Tri-Partite Panels 2/3/43, 1943 (Box 51, Folder 21)
- Memoranda to Panel Members and Hearing Officers, 1945 (Box 51, Folder 22)
- Nat'l. Wage Stabilization Board - Organization & Procedure 5/46, 1946 (Box 51, Folder 23)
- NWLB Training Program, 1945 (Box 51, Folder 24)
- Orders, Executive, 1945-1946 (Box 51, Folder 25)
- Orders, General, 1946 (Box 51, Folder 26)
- Organization & Procedures 8/44, 1944 (Box 51, Folder 27)
- Organization & Procedures 3/45, 1945 (Box 51, Folder 28)
- Policy Development Appraisal No. 1 1-5/45, 1945 (Box 51, Folder 29)
- Policy Development Appraisal No. 2 6/45, 1945 (Box 51, Folder 30)
- Policy Development Appraisal No. 3 7/45, 1945 (Box 51, Folder 31)
- Regional Rulings Which Were Reversed, Modified or Remanded, 1945 (Box 52, Folder 1)
- Region 2, NWLB - Termination Report, 1945 (Box 52, Folder 2)
- Wage Adjustment Board - Summary of Policy in the Building and Construction Industry - Region 2 3/22/46, 1946 (Box 52, Folder 3)
- Wage Forms, 1945 (Box 52, Folder 4)
- Wage-Price Policy, 1946 (Box 52, Folder 5)
- Wage Report to the President 2/22/45, 1945 (Box 52, Folder 6)
- Wage Stabilization Code - Application 7/44, 1944 (Box 52, Folder 7)
- Wage Stabilization - General Orders and Interpretations, 1945 (Box 52, Folder 8)
- Wage Stabilization, January 1942 to December 1944 4/1/45, 1945 (Box 52, Folder 9)
- Wage Stabilization Manual 6/1/44, 1944 (Box 52, Folder 10)
- Wage Stabilization Manual (June?) 45, 1945 (Box 52, Folder 11)
- Sample Agreements, 1944 (Box 52, Folder 12)
- Press Releases - Index to Releases of Nat'l. Board 12/45, 1945 (Box 52, Folder 13)
- Press Releases 4/20/44= 10/28/44, 1944 (Box 52, Folder 14)
- Press Releases 11/1/44 - 12/30/44, 1944 (Box 52, Folder 15)
- Press Releases 1/3/45 - 2/28/45, 1945 (Box 52, Folder 16)
- Press Releases 3/7/45 - 4/28/45, 1945 (Box 52, Folder 17)
- Press Releases 5/5/45 - 8/30/45, 1945 (Box 52, Folder 18)
- Press Releases 9/1/45 - 12/29/45, 1945 (Box 52, Folder 19)
- Press Releases 1/4/46 - 12/12/46, 1946 (Box 52, Folder 20)
- LPS - 1942 (Box 52, Folder 21)
- LPS - July, 1943 (Box 52, Folder 22)
- LPS - August, 1943 (Box 52, Folder 23)
- LPS - September, 1943 (Box 52, Folder 24)
- LPS - October, 1943 (Box 52, Folder 25)
- LPS - November, 1943 (Box 52, Folder 26)
- LPS - December, 1943 (Box 52, Folder 27)
- LPS - January, 1944 (Box 52, Folder 28)
- LPS - February, 1944 (Box 52, Folder 29)
- LPS - March, 1944 (Box 52, Folder 30)
- LPS - April, 1944 (Box 52, Folder 31)
- LPS - May, 1944 (Box 52, Folder 32)
- LPS - June, 1944 (Box 52, Folder 33)
- LPS - July, 1944 (Box 52, Folder 34)
- LPS - August, 1944 (Box 52, Folder 35)
- LPS - September, 1944 (Box 52, Folder 36)
- LPS - October, 1944 (Box 52, Folder 37)
- LPS - November, 1944 (Box 52, Folder 38)
- LPS - December, 1944 (Box 52, Folder 39)
- LPS - February, 1945 (Box 53, Folder 1)
- LPS - January, 1945 (Box 53, Folder 2)
- LPS - March, 1945 (Box 53, Folder 3)
- LPS - April, 1945 (Box 53, Folder 4)
- LPS - May, 1945 (Box 53, Folder 5)
- #30 - Board Policy In Regard To The Reinstatement of Employees After Strikes and/or Discharge, 1945 (Box 53, Folder 6)
- #5 - Statistical Survey of Changes in the American Economy, 1942-1943 (Box 53, Folder 7)
- #5A - Statistical Summary Part 2, 1944 (Box 53, Folder 8)
- #8 - Check-Off, 1943 (Box 53, Folder 9)
- #9 - National War Labor Board and the Control of Wages, 1943 (Box 53, Folder 10)
- #10 - Policy of the NWLB Regarding Types of Union Security Differing From the Standard Maintenance of Membership Prov., 1943 (Box 53, Folder 11)
- #12 - Industrial Disputes in Great Britain and the U.S., 1943 (Box 53, Folder 12)
- #14 - Compliance Record of The NWLB, 1943 (Box 53, Folder 13)
- #15 - The Effects of the War Upon the Relative, 1939 (Box 53, Folder 14)
- #17 - The NWLB Policies in Leading Wage Cases Involving Manpower, Part 1, 1944 (Box 53, Folder 15)
- #18 - The NWLB Policies in Leading Wage Cases Involving Manpower, Part 2, 1944 (Box 53, Folder 16)
- #20 - The Settlement of Jurisdictional Disputes in War Time, 1944 (Box 53, Folder 17)
- #21 - NWLB Cases Acted on by the Director of Economic Stabilization - October 2, 1942 to February 12, 1944, 1942-1944 (Box 53, Folder 18)
- #16 - Operations of Section 8 of the War Labor Disputes Act, 1943 (Box 53, Folder 19)
- @22 - Wartime Strikes and Controls in Great Britain, Canada, Australia and New Zealand, 1944 (Box 53, Folder 20)
- #23 - Comparison of Incentive Plans in the Airframe Industry, 1944 (Box 53, Folder 21)
- #24 - Estimated Frequency Distribution of Non-Agricultural Employees By Straight-Time Wage Rates, January 1944 (Box 53, Folder 22)
- #26 - Grievance Procedure Problems, 1944 (Box 53, Folder 23)
- #19 - Arbitration, 1944 (Box 53, Folder 24)
- #27 - Intra-Plant Wage Relationships, Part 1, 1944 (Box 53, Folder 25)
- #28 - Veterans Reinstatement and Seniority Rights, 1944 (Box 53, Folder 26)
- #29 - Intra-Plant Wage Relationships, Part 2, 1945 (Box 53, Folder 27)
- 331 - Review of Economic Trends, 1945 (Box 53, Folder 28)
- #32 - NWLB Policy on Equal Pay For Equal For Women, 1945 (Box 53, Folder 29)
- Summary of Wage Rate Brackets - Region 1 5/31/45, 1945 (Box 53, Folder 30)
- Summary of Wage Rate Brackets - Region 2 8/31/45, 1945 (Box 53, Folder 31)
- Summary of Wage Rate Brackets - Region VIII 8/31/45, 1945 (Box 53, Folder 32)
- Summary of Wage Rate Brackets - Region V 8/31/45, 1945 (Box 53, Folder 33)
- Summary of Wage Rate Brackets - Region IX 6/30/45, 1945 (Box 53, Folder 34)
- Summary of Wage Rate Brackets - Region X 5/31/45, 1945 (Box 53, Folder 35)
- Public Information Fact Sheets, 1945 (Box 53, Folder 36)